Lapis Lazuli Academy
Lady Tiararose!
Tomorrow is our graduation.
It's so sad to think
that I won't see you anymore.
We'll have opportunities to meet again.
I'll always be here
in the Kingdom of Lapis Lazuli.
Tiararose Lapis Clamentile
Yes, you're right!
Marietta
Fleuriane
You are the future queen, after all!
When is your wedding to Prince Hartknights?
After graduation, I'll undergo
bridal training for a year,
and then we will hold our
wedding in the cathedral.
Once you are queen, peace
in Lapis Lazuli will be assured.
I will do my best to live up
to everyone's expectations.
I am Tiararose Lapis Clamentile,
the daughter of the marquis
who was bestowed the Lapis name
and fiancée of the crown prince.
Prince Hartknights.
What's this?
His expression looks somewhat grim.
Has something happened?
Prince Hartknights!
Why?
This can't be!
After all, I am...
Huh?
I am...
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
A Love That Begins With the Ending
Prince Hartknights is gorgeous!
He's truly gorgeous.
Hartknights
I want you to live with me...
now and forever.
Yes
No
Of course!
Hartknights
I want you to live with me...
now and forever.
Yes
No
Sweet! A new event CG!
And that's the Hartknights route cleared!
The otome game, The Ring of Lapis Lazuli.
The Ring of Lapis Lazuli
I loved it so much, I couldn't put it down.
How dare you?
Tiararose
You're just a lowly commoner.
You need to stay away from my Hartknights.
Tiararose
You're an eyesore.
Is that me?
I remember now.
That was my previous life.
The Ring of Lapis Lazuli
And that young lady
with the nasty attitude is...
No... I'm...
a villainess?
I reincarnated as a villainess...
You're awake?
Your Highness!
You should get some more sleep.
I'm arranging a carriage for you now.
Hartknights Lapislazuli Lactomuth.
First Prince of the Kingdom of Lapis Lazuli
Hartknights Lapislazuli Lactomuth
He's the main route in the otome game
and the first prince
of the Kingdom of Lapis Lazuli.
A character in the game I played
is right in front of me!
You passing out like that is a first.
Were you trying to catch my eye because
I was giving Akari so much attention?
Huh?
His eyes are so cold.
He's nothing like the Hartknights in the game.
No. I seem to be a bit under the weather.
I apologize for the trouble.
Well, I am your fiancé, technically.
"Technically."
I know tomorrow is the graduation party,
but I have business to attend to.
I apologize, but I don't think
I'll be able to escort you there.
I understand.
Is there any greater humiliation than
not being escorted to a party by your fiancé?!
But I know what happens
in the story from this point on,
The Ring of Lapis Lazuli
because I played the game so many times.
The main route in the game
is the crown prince of the Kingdom
of Lapis Lazuli, Hartknights.
The heroine enrolls at the academy
with her powerful magic, the Holy Prayer,
and meets Hartknights.
He's the most popular student there,
and he constantly showers
the heroine with affection.
He smiles kindly at her,
whispers sweet lines to her...
and after the ending scene, they have
a grand wedding at the cathedral.
But I'm not the heroine.
I'm the villainess.
Know your place! You're only a commoner!
Tiararose
Know your place!
You're only a commoner!
Tiararose
I am a more suitable
match for His Highness.
Tiararose the villainess
treats the heroine harshly
Tiararose
You're in my way! Move!
because she doesn't want to lose the prince.
At the graduation party, she's condemned
for her contempt of the heroine,
and her engagement is called off.
Tiararose
Grr! How infuriating!
But I haven't done anything that mean.
I'd like to avoid the condemnation
event if I can, but...
Today is the day before the game's ending.
The condemnation event
is unavoidable at this point.
Only a bad ending awaits me.
What happens to the villainess
after the condemnation event, again?
I do know this much:
there is no happy ending where
the villainess ends up with someone.
Welcome home, Lady Tiararose.
Philine Sunfist
Thank you, Philine.
The Lapis name is an honor
bestowed upon the families
of those who perform great deeds
for the royal family.
Welcome home, Tiararose.
Welcome home.
Thank you.
What brought this on?
You rarely welcome me home personally.
Prime Minister
Schnauss Lapis Clamentile
Iltiana Lapis Clamentile
We found a lovely accessory you can wear
at your wedding with the prince.
I was so excited to show you.
And we received some of the sweets you like.
Let's eat them together.
You won't have many more
opportunities to eat sweets.
Now, dear, it's too soon to start crying.
I know that. I'll miss Tiara,
but her happiness comes first.
As the daughter of the marquis
who was granted the Lapis name,
I've been undergoing training
to become queen since I was young.
As the crown prince's fiancée,
I've worked hard at studying
all sorts of subjects.
If it seems like your husband
is about to take a wrong turn,
make sure you correct him.
My father, the prime minister, taught me that.
It may have been strenuous at times,
but I did it all out of love
for Prince Hartknights.
But... it seems that didn't get
through to Prince Hartknights.
I loved his character, too...
Maybe I'll just skip
tomorrow's graduation party.
No, I can't.
It would be a bad look for the daughter of
the marquis with the Lapis name to be absent.
The last thing I want to do
is trouble my dear mother and father.
Hartknights' change of heart
is in line with the game's story.
I can't change my own role
as the villainess, either.
If I were the heroine,
I could've had a happy ending,
but I don't know what's
going to happen to me now...
What's going to happen to me?
Lady Tiararose...
If I could have my way, you would...
The Villainess Is Adored
by the Prince of the Neighbor Kingdom
The Day of the Condemnation Event
Lady Akari's behavior is simply too much!
It certainly is!
How dare she hang all over Prince Hartknights
when his fiancée,
Lady Tiararose, is right here?
No matter what happens,
Lady Tiararose, we're on your side!
Thank you. That's very reassuring.
The condemnation event we all call
a graduation party will soon begin.
I prepared myself for this,
but I'm still scared.
Lady Tiararose...
Perhaps I should contact the master
and have him escort you?
It's all right, Philine.
Father has his own work to do.
I couldn't trouble him.
Yes, but...
Still... you're right.
If Father were to see me enter
the party without an escort,
he would surely go mad with rage.
Excessively Doting Daddy
I'm still worried about you, Lady Tiararose.
I'll be just fine.
Oh, those look delicious!
Please, help yourself.
Gladly!
Delicious!
I've loved baking and eating sweets
ever since my previous life.
Eating delicious sweets makes me feel happy.
Philine, did you bring these
to try to cheer me up?
I hoped it would make you smile,
even if only for a moment.
Philine...
I can't avoid the condemnation event,
so there's no point
in sitting around being afraid!
I have to try my best!
Lady Tiara! Are you feeling all right?
Lady Akari, you can't
just enter unannounced!
Well, good day to you, Lady Akari.
And thank you for your concern.
Good day to you, Lady Tiara.
Akari
I'm pretty sure she's the heroine of
the otome game The Ring of Lapis Lazuli.
A cute, luxurious dress...
Shining jewels...
The sweet nature of an angel...
She's everything you'd expect
the game's heroine to be.
I was worried after you suddenly collapsed
in the classroom yesterday.
Prince Hartknights was concerned, as well.
He's so kind, isn't he?
I apologize for worrying you.
Prince Hartknights.
Good day, Your Highness.
Of course. Akari was worried
after you passed out, after all.
How are you feeling?
Will you make it to the graduation party?
Yes, I had a good night's rest,
so it won't be a problem.
It's such a relief to see that you're all right!
Isn't it, Prince Hartknights?
Yes, it is.
Philine, we'll need to make the final
preparations soon if I'm to make it on time.
Of course.
What?! Lady Tiara, you aren't even ready yet?
Looks like we arrived at a busy time for her.
We'll be taking our leave now.
All right.
Once these doors are opened, it will begin.
Tiararose Lapis Clamentile
is entering the venue.
It's begun.
Just like in the game.
What's going on?
Why is Lady Tiararose entering alone?
Who's that girl beside the prince?
Tiararose, I hereby
call off my engagement with you!
Would you mind telling me the reason?
The reason?
Tiararose, why don't you try asking yourself?
I don't know what could be.
I've done nothing deserving of shame.
If you wish to take
someone else as your consort,
are there not proper procedures
you need to follow?
How dare you talk back
to a member of the royal family?!
You said many harsh things to Akari
after learning that she
grew up in the countryside!
She seemed to be unaware
of our kingdom's laws,
so I simply taught her a few times.
Well, I heard you told her
to kneel when greeting me!
Well, Your Highness is the crown prince.
It is common sense that she
should kneel when greeting you!
And you told her not to dance with me, too!
That's because she had already
danced with you more than twice.
That is something only your fiancée can do.
You're not going to tell me
you didn't know that, are you?
B-But Akari said you're always cruel to her!
No amount of defending my
innocence will do any good.
Whether it's because the heroine conquered him
or it's a revision to the game,
it all goes according to the story in the end.
I guess the ending can't be changed after all.
So your heart belongs to Lady Akari, then?
You accept the breaking
of our engagement, yes?
Yes.
Then, I hereby end my engagement with you
and will be engaged to Akari.
In other words, Akari will be the future queen!
It's over.
But I still have my kind parents,
as well as Philine and my friends.
I haven't lost everything—
The crime of harming the future queen...
is not a crime that can be forgiven!
What?
Therefore, Tiararose, I hereby
banish you from this kingdom!
Banish... me?
No... That's too cruel!
I can't defy the crown prince.
If I'm banished, I won't be able
to see any of them again.
Not my father, or my mother,
or even Philine...
No!
That is enough.
Are you all right, Lady Tiararose?
Prince Aquasteed?
The first prince
of the Kingdom of Marinforest...
First Prince of the Kingdom of Marinforest
Aquasteed Marinforest
Aquasteed.
He's the main character
of the game's sequel.
I fell in love the moment
I first saw his design.
But I died before the sequel
was even released.
What is Prince Aquasteed doing here?
It's all right. Stand tall.
You, in all your pride, are more
righteous than anyone here...
and more beautiful.
Prince Aquasteed,
could you stay out of this?
She must be condemned for her crimes!
Condemned?
It seems to me that your words
have been far harsher than hers.
Breaking your engagement at a
graduation party, a celebratory event,
criticizing a lone woman
in front of everyone
and humiliating her...
These are not things
a crown prince should do.
Wh-What business is it of yours?!
It is my business.
Very much so.
Your engagement is over now, correct?
Lady Tiararose, would you be my consort?
What?
I have wanted desperately
to make you mine for a long time.
What? For a... long time?
Wait, why is the prince
from the sequel proposing to me?
Wait, he's proposing?!
I'm sure my sudden proposal
comes as a surprise to you.
But would you please consider it?
Thank you.
Hearing how you feel has made me very happy.
Wait!
This is unbelievable!
Lady Tiara was Prince Hartknights'
fiancée until just a moment ago!
Why would you choose her?!
Lady Tiara is terribly mean and belligerent!
She isn't fit for you!
So please... come and join us!
Lady Akari!
Prince Aquasteed is the crown prince
of our neighboring kingdom!
You mustn't simply touch him like that!
Please let go of him!
No! I won't let you have Prince Aqua—
Thank you for showing such concern
for me, Lady Tiararose.
Not at all...
I am the first prince of Marinforest.
You know this, and you still
choose to behave this way?
Wh-What?
But you are very kind, Prince Aqua.
You wouldn't get angry over such a...
She disrespects me. Take her away.
Huh?
What?! But why?!
What?!
It seems I've caused confusion
by suddenly getting involved.
I do apologize, Lady Tiararose.
Oh, no, not at all.
I should thank you for helping me.
I would help you at any time.
We should be past the game's ending already...
What's going to happen now?!
Prince Aqua, Do You Like Sugar?
I never dreamed Prince Aquasteed
would propose to me...
Your Highness, please don't spoil me so.